question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Art",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Leonardo da Vince's Mona Lisa does not have eyebrows.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "There was a satirical candidate named 'Deez Nuts' running "
                    "in the 2016 US presidential elections.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The book 1984 was published in 1949.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Faust is a playable character in 'Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator'.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in "
                    "response to the September 11th attacks.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The card game &quot;Munchkin&quot; won the 2001 Origins Award for "
                    "Best Traditional Card Game.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of "
                    "Star Wars during and after filming.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, "
                    "causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In 'Space Station 13',  the station has a clown aboard it.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]
